tryingfitness.com 2010-12-31

# Privacy Policy

Don't miss out! Find out why thousands of people are Team Beachbody Club members. [Sign up for free!](http://coacheartha.com/tbbclub/community.php)

 **Our Commitment to Privacy**  
We use industry standard safeguards to protect the confidentiality of personal information we collect from visitors to this Web site. Personal information collected is accessible only by designated staff or agents of our organization who are also bound to this statement. It is important to recognize that perfect security does not exist on the Internet. This statement is provided to clarify our commitment to protecting the security of the personal information you provide.

Personal Information that We May Collect When you register on our site, we may ask for information such as your name, email address, postal address, zip code, telephone, gender, personal interests and preferences of our products and services. We do not collect or maintain information from those actually known to be under the age of 13. We will not contact children under age 13 without a parent’s permission.

In addition to the information provided by Web site visitors, our computers automatically receive and record information from your Internet browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the pages you request.

**How We Use and Disclose Your Information**  
We use information you provide on an aggregated basis to do such things as operate our site, enhance our site, and to better understand the profile of our online audience. We may also use this data, both aggregate and personal to you, to enhance your site experience on our site by displaying content and marketing messages that we believe will be of interest to you. In some cases we use your personal information to contact you or to provide information to you, such as to send newsletters to you that you request.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
We do not sell or rent your personal information or share your personal information with other people or nonaffiliated companies, except with your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We may provide the information to trusted partners who work our behalf under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help us communicate with you about offers. These companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Web site terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if this company is acquired by or merges with another company.
  * Third parties (hackers) may unlawfully intercept or access information or confidential transmissions.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Methods**  
Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your computer. We may use cookies or, in a limited number of cases and IP addresses for a number of reasons. Cookies allow us to better understand how users use our site and can help us to tailor our Web site or a marketing message to better match your needs and interests. Cookies can also help you remember your user name and password on protected areas of Web sites. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our site may not work properly if you do.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.TryingFitness.com
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.TryingFitness.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.TryingFitness.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.TryingFitness.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.TryingFitness.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**Notification of Changes**  
Correction of Personal Information; Opt-Out Right We ask that you notify us of any changes to your personal information via our contact form.

You may at any time request to be removed from our email list by clicking the unsubscribe link in any email you receive from us. Alternatively, you may notify us via our contact form. In the event you elect not to receive any future contacts from us, we will endeavor to remove your name from our email list within 10 business days.

If we are going to use your personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection through this Web site, we will notify you. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that affect user information already collected through our site, we will post a notice on our web site notifying users of the change.
